theleesshop.com 2014-05-23

# ::::Theleesshop:::: All mens slim & luxury items

|  |   
---  
    
+ Shirts  
   Hoodies  
   Hood Zipup  
   Cardigans  
+ Outerwear  
   Jeans  
+ Pants  
   Shorts  
+ Athletic Apparel  
+ Suits  
   Underwear  
+ Shoes  
+ Bags  
+ Accessories  
+ SET ITEM  
   Shapewear  
    
   Tees  
   Knits  
   Shirts/Blouses  
   Tanks/Camis  
   Tunics  
   Jackets  
   Coats  
   Cardigans  
   Vests  
   Dresses  
   Jump Suit  
   Skirts  
   Jeans  
   Pants  
   Shorts  
   Leggings  
   Bags  
   Shapewear  
   Shoes  

|   
---  
We respect the privacy of our visitors/customers, which is extremely important to us. We take your online safety seriously. To better serve you and to make you understand how your information is used on our site, we have explained our privacy policy below.  
**1\. The information we collect**  
We believe it’s important for you to know what types of information we collect when you use our site. The information includes your Email, Name, Company Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Telephone Number, Password and so on. We collect this information in several different ways; to begin with, we use cookies that are needed to compile and aggregate non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our web site. Personally identifiable information consists of information that is unique to you, such as credit card number and bank account numbers. The information is unique to you.   
**2\. The use of information**  
Help us make this site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.  
Helps you quickly locate information, products, and services.  
Helps us create content on this site that is most relevant to you.  
Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.   
Registration and Ordering:  
During registration, you will be prompted to provide us your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address and credit card number. In addition, we may also ask you for your country so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations, and we might also ask for your gender. These types of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide us with to contact you.  
  
Email Addresses:  
You register for placing an order and receiving free promotional notices; we notify you when we receive a new brand, or new product style; to get there great offers, you simply sign up for our email newsletter. Your participation in a contest is completely voluntary, and you may choose whether to participate and disclose information to us.   
**3\. Privacy Security**  
We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business. We use the latest in encryption technology, and all employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities.   
What kind of email do you send to the customer?   
We send email content to our customers that may include following:  
Transaction mail, Shipping notification, Weekly deal, Promotion, Activity,  
  
      Address, Phone Number and Email   
      Sang Min Lee. 36-1 1BF, Songgang-dong, Yuseong-gu Daejeon, 305-802, Korea, South   
      Phone: +82-70-4640-4283  
      Email: thelees.cs@gmail.com  
  
How do I unsubscribe?  
You can unsubscribe from any email via your subscribe settings after you log in.   
|   
---  

**C/S Center** : Tel +82-70-4640-5045   |    **E-mail** : thelees.cs@gmail.com  
**Hours :** Monday - Friday 10:00 a.m.~ 5:00 p.m.  
**Business License Number:** 314-86-31099   
**Address** : 688, Bongsan-dong, Yuseong-gu, Daejeon, South Korea (305-506)  
Copyright(c)2012. theleesshop.com All rights reserved.
